Guide to the Pauline Bart papers, 1925-2008 and undated, bulk 1969-1995 RL.10069
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiotapes Series, 1974-1994; undated; 1
  - Women in Science Study Group, 1973 December; 24
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0022)
  - Bart, Potter, Pricook, undated; 25
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0023)
  - Goldberg tape #2, undated; 26
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0024)
  - Radio program me Marlyn Lucy, undated; 27
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0025)
  - Jones Haifa Sexual Harassment, undated; 28
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0026)
  - Ann Arbor rape conference, Lynda Holmstrom at the end- Salt Lake, undated; 29
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0027)
  - Jan Weller- False Memories with Pauline Bart, WIS Public Radio, 1994 May 20; 30
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0028)
  - Anne's Speech at Portsmouth, Pauline's Speech at Portsmouth, undated; 31
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0029)
  - J. Pearlman, undated; 32
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0030)
  - Esther Kipp, Circa 1976-1977; 33
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0031)
  - Abby Pariser, Circa 1976-1977; 34
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0032)
  - Susan Miller, Circa 1976-1977; 35
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0033)
  - Judy Earle/Susan Montague, Circa 1976-1977; 36
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0034)
  - Sheila Smith, Circa 1976-1977; 37
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0035)
  - Judith P., 38
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0036)
  - Eileen Smith/Sheila Smith, 48
    - Original audiocassette (Box 90, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0046)
  - Unlabeled, 39
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0037)
  - Unlabeled, 40
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0038)
  - Unlabeled, 41
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0039)
  - Unlabeled, 42
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0040)
  - Unlabeled, 43
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0041)
  - Unlabeled, 44
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0042)
  - Unlabeled, 45
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0043)
  - Unlabeled, 46
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0044)
  - Unlabeled, 47
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0045)